const AgricQuestion = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the practice of cultivating soil, raising crops, and rearing animals for food, fiber, and other products?",
    options: ["Horticulture", "Agriculture", "Forestry", "Aquaculture"],
    answer: "Agriculture",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the growing of fruits, vegetables, flowers, and ornamental plants?",
    options: ["Farming", "Ranching", "Horticulture", "Aquaculture"],
    answer: "Horticulture",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the process of raising and breeding fish, crustaceans, and aquatic plants for consumption?",
    options: ["Horticulture", "Agriculture", "Forestry", "Aquaculture"],
    answer: "Aquaculture",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the management and cultivation of trees for timber production?",
    options: ["Horticulture", "Agriculture", "Forestry", "Aquaculture"],
    answer: "Forestry",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the primary source of food, fiber, and fuel for human consumption and industrial processes?",
    options: ["Plants", "Animals", "Fungi", "Bacteria"],
    answer: "Plants",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural activity involves the raising of livestock such as cattle, sheep, and goats?",
    options: ["Farming", "Ranching", "Horticulture", "Aquaculture"],
    answer: "Ranching",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the agricultural term for the process of removing weeds from cultivated land?",
    options: [
      "Fertilization",
      "Irrigation",
      "Pesticide application",
      "Weeding",
    ],
    answer: "Weeding",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the application of water to land to assist in the growth of crops?",
    options: [
      "Fertilization",
      "Irrigation",
      "Pesticide application",
      "Weeding",
    ],
    answer: "Irrigation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the process of artificially adding nutrients to soil to enhance plant growth?",
    options: [
      "Fertilization",
      "Irrigation",
      "Pesticide application",
      "Weeding",
    ],
    answer: "Fertilization",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the application of chemicals to control pests and diseases in crops?",
    options: [
      "Fertilization",
      "Irrigation",
      "Pesticide application",
      "Weeding",
    ],
    answer: "Pesticide application",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the agricultural practice of rotating crops in a sequence over several seasons to improve soil health and fertility?",
    options: ["Monoculture", "Polyculture", "Crop rotation", "Agroforestry"],
    answer: "Crop rotation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural method involves the use of organic materials, such as compost and manure, to improve soil structure and fertility?",
    options: [
      "Conventional farming",
      "No-till farming",
      "Organic farming",
      "Hydroponics",
    ],
    answer: "Organic farming",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the process of transferring pollen from the male reproductive organs to the female reproductive organs of a flower?",
    options: ["Pollination", "Fertilization", "Germination", "Propagation"],
    answer: "Pollination",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the breeding and raising of honeybees for the production of honey and pollination of crops?",
    options: ["Apiculture", "Sericulture", "Aquaculture", "Aviculture"],
    answer: "Apiculture",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the removal of excess water from soil to improve drainage and prevent waterlogging?",
    options: ["Fertilization", "Irrigation", "Drainage", "Land leveling"],
    answer: "Drainage",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the cultivation of crops without disturbing the soil through plowing or tilling?",
    options: [
      "Conventional farming",
      "No-till farming",
      "Organic farming",
      "Hydroponics",
    ],
    answer: "No-till farming",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the process of separating harvested grains from the chaff using airflow?",
    options: ["Threshing", "Winnowing", "Harvesting", "Sorting"],
    answer: "Winnowing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural method involves the cultivation of crops in water, without soil?",
    options: ["Hydroponics", "Aquaponics", "Aeroponics", "Vertical farming"],
    answer: "Hydroponics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the term for the process of artificially reproducing plants from seeds, cuttings, or tissue culture?",
    options: ["Pollination", "Fertilization", "Germination", "Propagation"],
    answer: "Propagation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which agricultural practice involves the cultivation of silkworms for the production of silk?",
    options: ["Apiculture", "Sericulture", "Aquaculture", "Aviculture"],
    answer: "Sericulture",
  },
];

export default AgricQuestion;
